<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tabs</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>

    <string name="hello_first_fragment">Hello first fragment</string>
    <string name="hello_second_fragment">Hello second fragment. Arg: %1$s</string>
    
    <string name="add_plant_ask_name">"I’m glad you made a new friend! What’s their name?"</string>
    <string name="add_plant_ask_stage">And where are you and %1$s in your friendship? </string>
    <string name="add_plant_place_plant">Great, let’s put %1$s here.</string>
    <string name="del_plant_check">"I’m sorry to hear that, are you sure?"</string>
    <string name="del_plant_no">"I understand, friendships can be hard sometimes. I’m rooting for you!"</string>
    <string name="del_plant_yes">Okay, let me take care of it.</string>
    <string name="spam_water_can">
        I noticed that you watered %1$s a lot recently, I’m glad your friendship is going strong. Remember though, relationships take time to grow, just like plants!
    </string>
    <string name="bob_introduction">Hi there! What can I help you with today?</string>
    <string name="bob_option_addgrow_plant">
        You can add a new plant, or grow a seed, by clicking on an empty pot. Each time you catch up with your friend, remember to come back and water the plant. Happy growing!
    </string>
    <string name="bob_option_wilt">
        "Have you noticed your plants wilting? That’s what happens when you haven’t watered them in a while. This is a good reminder to schedule brunch to catch up or send a \“How are you doing?\” text to keep your friendship going strong!"
    </string>
    <string name="bob_option_del_plant">"I’m sorry to hear that there’s a plant you want to remove. Go to the plant’s page and click on the shovel icon. I’ll take care of it from there."</string>
    <string name="bob_option_encourage">Staying connected to friends will help you lower stress, find support, and stay healthy!</string>
    <string name="bob_plant_wilt">Oh no your plant is wilting! Remember to catch up with %1$s soon, and then water your plant by clicking the water jug icon!</string>
    <string name="bob_plant_congrats">Wow! Your plant looks healthy. Cheers to %1$d days of friendship.</string>

    
    
    
    
</resources>
